// Geography Questions
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "India is part of what continent?",
    answer: "Asia",
    options: [
      "Africa",
      "Asia",
      "Oceania",
      "Northern Hemisphere"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is a large landmass that juts out from a continent called?",
    answer: "Sub-continent",
    options: [
      "Island",
      "Pennisula",
      "Sub-continent",
      "None of the Above"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What river in India begins in the Himalyas and empties into the Arabian Sea?",
    answer: "Indus",
    options: [
      "Amazon",
      "Nile",
      "Ganges",
      "Indus"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What Indian river flows from the Himalayas innto the Bay of Bengel?",
    answer: "Ganges",
    options: [
      "Amazon",
      "Ganges",
      "Nile",
      "Indus"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The major mountain ranges in Northern India are called?",
    answer: "Himalayas and Hindu Kush",
    options: [
      "Himalayas and Everest",
      "Himalayas and Hindu Kush",
      "Himalayas and Indus",
      "Himalyas and Ganges"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "The three bodies of water surrounding India are:",
  answer: "Bay of Bengel, Arabian Sea, and Indian Ocean",
  options: [
    "Bay of Bengel, Arabian Sea, and Pacific Ocean",
    "Persian Gulf, Arabian Sea, and Pacific Ocean",
    "Bay of Bengel, Arabian Sea, and Indian Ocean",
    "Bay of Bengel, Mediterranean Sea, and Indian Ocean"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "The name of the highest mountain in the world is____________",
  answer: "Mt. Everest",
  options: [
    "Mt. Himalaya",
    "Mt. Everest",
    "Mt. Hindu Kush",
    "Mt. Arash"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "The winter monsoons come from which direction?",
  answer: "The northeast",
  options: [
    "The northwest",
    "The northeast",
    "The southwest",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "The winter monsoons bring what kind of air?",
  answer: "Dry",
  options: [
    "Wet",
    "Dry",
    "Semi wet",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "This is the most populated city in India",
  answer: "Bombay",
  options: [
    "Calcutta",
    "Bombay",
    "Delhi",
    "Madras"
  ]
},

];
